<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to guides on Born in Bradford Data Dictionary</title>
    <link>https://borninbradford.github.io/datadict/how-to/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to guides on Born in Bradford Data Dictionary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://borninbradford.github.io/datadict/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data dictionary structure</title>
      <link>https://borninbradford.github.io/datadict/how-to/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borninbradford.github.io/datadict/how-to/structure/</guid>
      <description>The BiB data dictionary is organised into Variables, Tables, Projects and Cohorts.
Variables Variables contain data, usually about a person. The main purpose of the data dictionary is to hold information about each Variable, what it contains, who it relates to and when it was collected.
Tables Variables are organised into Tables, the characteristics of which can vary. Mostly, Tables gather Variables together from the same set of people collected over the same time period and in the same way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a data request</title>
      <link>https://borninbradford.github.io/datadict/how-to/data_request/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borninbradford.github.io/datadict/how-to/data_request/</guid>
      <description>When you request data from BiB you will need to send us a list of the Variables you need, along with the Tables and Projects they sit in. First of all, familiarise yourself with the structure of the data dictionary.
We need the list of Variables in the following format:
`&amp;lt;project_name&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;table_name&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;variable_name&amp;gt;` This is called the fully qualified Variable name.
The &amp;lt;project_name&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;table_name&amp;gt; part can be found at the top of each Table page and is called the Table ID.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>